He has the power to make you live his nightmares... And he's dreaming about you.
The Sender is a horror, thriller, science fiction
film directed by Roger Christian.
A disturbed telepathic man is able to transmit his dreams and
visions into the minds of the people around him.
Dr Gail Farmer, played by Kathryn Harrold.
John Doe #83, played by Zeljko Ivanek.
Jerolyn, played by Shirley Knight.
Dr Joseph Denman, played by Paul Freeman.
The Messiah, played by Sean Hewitt.
Dr Hirsch, played by Harry Ditson.
The Sender is a 1982 British supernatural horror film directed by Roger Christian, written by Thomas Baum, and
starring Kathryn Harrold, Željko Ivanek (in his film debut), Shirley Knight, and Paul Freeman.
The plot follows a therapist attempting to help a disturbed telepathic man able to
transmit his dreams and visions into the minds of those around him.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.